<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Game of Thrones</string>
    <string name="Arya_Desc">Maisie Williams plays Arya Stark, Ned and Catelyn Stark\'s most rebellious daughter. Arya is a young woman much more interested in wielding her sword than in becoming a lady. And because of that, she is constantly in conflict with her sister Sansa hers because she is much more prim. She hates dresses, prefers rags, and prefers exploring to having tea. Arya is a worthy daughter of her father, as she is very much like him and Ned appreciates the rebellious attitude of the girl, to some extent. Jon is the one who understands and empathizes with her the most, therefore, he will give her a very important gift. Her wolf is called Nymeria.</string>
    <string name="Cersei_desc">Lena Headey is Cersei Lannister in Game of Thrones. She is the wife of Robert Baratheon and queen of the Seven Kingdoms. Cersei Lannister is the only daughter of Tywin Lannister, former Hand of the King and the richest man in the Seven Kingdoms. She is a very manipulative and ambitious woman. She is married to Robert Baratheon and although she despises her husband, she adopts his last name and becomes queen of the Seven Kingdoms. She is the mother of her three children.She belongs to the Lannister house, in which she has two brothers: her twin, Jaime, with whom she maintains a close relationship; and the clever dwarf, Tyrion, whom she barely tolerates. Although her father originally wanted her to marry Rhaegar Targaryen, the proposal was rejected by the mad king Aerys.</string>
    <string name="Daenerys_desc">"Emilia Clarke plays Daenerys Targaryen in Game of Thrones, princess of the House of Targaryen. Daenerys Targaryen is the princess of House Targaryen, who was exiled to Essos. She knows nothing about Westeros, except what her brother Viserys tells her. The last two surviving Targaryens fled to Essos after Aerys, the mad king, was killed during Robert's rebellion. In addition, Daenerys is mistreated by her brother and is forcibly engaged to Khal Drogo, a stranger to her. Although at first she is afraid, her relationship with the people of her husband will make Daenerys become Khaleesi, lose her innocence and gain confidence and poise. "</string>
    <string name="Jon_desc">Kit Harington is Jon Snow in Game of Thrones, the bastard son of Ned Stark. He belongs to House Stark. Jon Snow is the bastard son of Lord Eddard Stark. Ambitious and brave, he has been raised in Winterfell on an equal footing with the rest of his siblings. He has a very good relationship with all the members of the Stark family, the only one who does not like him is Catelyn, his father\'s wife. The only problem is that being a bastard son, he does not have the same privileges as the rest of his siblings. Following in the footsteps of his Uncle Benjen, Jon joins the Night\'s Watch. His wolf is called Ghost.</string>
    <string name="Samwell_desc">John Bradley plays Jon Snow\'s friend Samwell Tarly in Game of Thrones. Samwell, better known as Sam, was forced to join the Night\'s Watch by his father as a means of disinheriting him. His \"cowardice\" and delicacy made Jon Snow bet on him from the beginning.</string>
    <string name="Sansa_desc">Sophie Turner plays Sansa Stark in Game of Thrones, the eldest daughter of Catelyn and Ned Stark. Sansa has inherited the beauty from her mother, Catelyn, which should be of great use to her in the court of knights and princes to which she dreams of belonging one day. But growing up in the Far North, where the hardships she experiences are only teased by her sister, has made her very protected. Besides, her naivety won\'t help him in the real world, outside the walls of Winterfell. Where not everything is as beautiful as it seems. His wolf is called Lady.</string>
</resources>